cakecentral.com 2019-12-17

# CakeCentral.com

## **Our Commitment to Privacy**

Our Privacy Policy was developed as an extension of our commitment to combine quality products and services with integrity in dealing with our users. The Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site and our products and services. 

## **What Information Do We Collect?**

When you visit our site you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you actively choose to disclose (Active Information) and information collected, in a way not visible to you, on an aggregate anonymous basis as you and others browse our site (Passive Information). 

## **No Use of Our Site by Persons Under 13**

No person under 13 should disclose information on this site. You may learn more about protecting children privacy online by visiting [_http://www.consumer.ftc.gov/articles/0031-protecting-your-childs-privacy-online_](https://www.consumer.ftc.gov/articles/0031-protecting-your-childs-privacy-online)

## **Active Information You Choose to Provide Cake Central Media Corp. - Contact and Personal Information**

In order to gain use of the site (become a user), we require you to provide your contact information during the registration process. This may include a name, email address, mailing address, and contact telephone number. This information is used to verify account ownership and to possibly contact you if there is a problem with your order. We also use your email address to send you notification emails that you have opted to receive in your user settings. 

At times, we may use your email address to send out a mailing to all users of the site to let them know about changes to the service or important updates. If we do use a newsletter for promotional purposes, it will have instructions on how to unsubscribe prominently mentioned in the mailing. Our newsletter also requires an opt-in before we start sending it to you. 

## **Placing an Order**

When you make a purchase from our site, we will require contact information (such as a name, email address, phone number, billing and shipping address) and financial information (such as a credit card number and expiration date). We use this information to process your order and to contact you if there are any issues with your order. 

## **Other Information**

If you choose to post information on our site or maintain email, snail mail or telephone contact with us, we may retain such information for customer service purposes. 

## **Passive Information Collected**

Our site utilizes a standard technology called cookies to collect information about how our site is used. Passive Information gathered may include the date and time of visits, the site pages viewed, time spent at our site, the sites visited just before and just after our site. Cookies are also used to store your login information so you don't have to enter a password on each area of our merchant management pages. Our shopping cart also uses cookies to store your shopping cart contents during your shopping session. This information is not shared with any third parties. 

Web pages may contain electronic images known as web beacons - sometimes called single-pixel gifs - that allow us to count users who have visited those pages we may include web beacons in promotional e-mail messages or Newsletters in order to count how many messages have been opened and acted upon. Web beacons are not used to access your personal information; they are a technique we use to compile aggregated statistics about website usage. 

## **What is a Cookie?**

Cookies are a feature of web browser (Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox, Netscape Navigator, etc.) software that allows web servers to recognize the computer used to access a site. They are small pieces of data that are stored by a user's web browser on one site to simplify subsequent interactions with that site by the same user or to use the information to streamline the user's transaction on related web pages. This makes it easier for a user to move from site to site and to complete transactions over the Internet. Cookies should make your online experience easier and more personalized. 

## **How Do We Use the Information Collected?**

Broadly speaking, persons we employ directly, or as contractors or agents at our direction use Active Information for purposes of administering our business activities, providing customer services such as support, and making available other products or services we think may be of interest to our users. We may use the Active Information or Passive Information you provide to us to contact you about changes to our site, new services, features or products we offer, or other information we think you shall find valuable. If at any time you do not wish to receive promotional information, you can opt out at any time. 

We use Passive Information to gather information about our users and to enhance and design our site to make it easier, faster and friendlier to use. Additionally, cookies help us know information about how many people visit our site, when they visit and how they use our service. We do not connect any of this information to your personal information or email address. 

## **Your Information In Relation to Others We Link To**

You may be able to access other web sites through our site. When you do so you are doing so subject to their policies regarding privacy and data collection and you should read those site's privacy policies to make sure you agree to them before using such sites. When you choose to shop at such sites, you should read their privacy policies to make sure you agree to them before making purchases. 

## **Sharing Information with the Government or As Otherwise Required by Law**

Cake Central Media Corp. cooperates with law enforcement inquiries, as well as other third parties to enforce laws, such as: intellectual property rights, fraud and other rights. We can (and you authorize us to) disclose any information about you to law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate, in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that is illegal or may expose us or you to legal liability. 

## **How Do We Secure Information?**

We secure your personal information submitted by you by using reasonable efforts to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, or accidental loss or destruction of Active Information and Passive Information. Your postings on this site and other communications you may have with us via email or snail mail may not be secure unless we advise you that security measures are in place prior to your sending information. Therefore, if you choose to communicate with us through these means, you are assuming the risk of doing so and we request that you do not send or post sensitive information through these means. _When placing an order, all sensitive information is sent through a secure server with 256bit Encryption._

## **How Can You Choose Not to Receive Information about Products or Services by Us or to Correct, Delete or Access Your Information**

If you desire not to receive information about products or services we think may be of interest to you or if you wish to access, delete or correct your information, please contact us at support@cakecentral.com. 

We reserve the right to revise this policy at our discretion. Please check back on this site as this policy may be revised from time to time without notice to you. 

For information about opting out of Gourmet Ads and ad serving partners please visit _<http://www.gourmetads.com/about/privacy-policy>_

_We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies,_[ _click here_](https://www.networkadvertising.org/) _._  

## **Contact Information**

Our homepage on the Internet is located at [_http://www.cakecentral.com_](https://www.cakecentral.com/). 

**Cake Central Media Corp.**  
20701 N Scottsdale Rd STE 107-476   
Scottsdale AZ 85255   
United States   
P: (866) 878-3133 
  *[P:]: Phone
